dsogaming.com 2019-12-27

# Privacy Policy - DSOGaming

##### Privacy Policy – [www.dsogaming.com](https://www.dsogaming.com/)

#####  **What information we collect**

#####  To prevent abuse and enhance the features of our site, we collect non-personal information such as the IP (internet provider). Sometimes, we may store a file called a cookie on your computer. These non-malicious files are set to delete themselves within a short period of time (usually one day). They are used by us to help our advertisers target their traffic. A cookie may also be saved on your computer by our ad providers (ValueForClick, and Google Adsense) when you click an ad. This is saved on your computer so the advertisers can tell that you’ve already clicked an ad. This saves our advertisers from paying for double and fraudulent clicks.

##### We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our DSOGaming.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

#####  **We only collect necessary information**

##### The information we collect is only the information which is necessary. No personally identifiable information (such as your phone number, address, name etc) is ever collected unless you have willingly submitted it such as through registration.

#####  **Sites like DSOGaming  use cookies, files which stay on your PC, and you can turn that feature off in your browser if you’re not comfortable with it. There are 3rd-party adverts on this site, and they often collate traffic data and use cookies. You can block their tracking with systems like this one, or any number of other cookie blockers available on the web, such as [Spybot](http://www.safer-networking.org/index2.html).**

#####  **Security**

##### To ensure the highest amount of privacy,  DSOGaming.com is equipped with many security features to protect our files from unauthorized access.

##### Third-Party Tools

##### We use Disqus Comments at our website for you to be able to comment at our webpages using Disqus commenting system. Disqus may collect information about you when you register for and use the Service. Such information may include “Personally Identifiable Information” which means information that identifies you as an individual, such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, telephone number, username or account ID, and “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” which means information that does not identify you as an individual. Non-Personally Identifiable Information may include, but is not limited to, information about your browser, your IP address, device ID, what pages you visit on our Partner Sites, which website you came from, what advertisements you clicked on, whether on our Partner Websites, the Service or other third party websites, and other information about your online activity that does not identify you as an individual, in accordance with their data privacy policy: <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>

##### DSOGaming uses some third-party plugins that send request to third party APIs via website-visitor’s web browser to fetch information (like social shares, social comment count). This request made by web browser may include IP address, which can then be seen by the third-party that it’s being requested from. This API request doesn’t include any personal data of the website user other than the IP address.

#####  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

##### The contents of this policy may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

##### If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of, please contact us at [john2@dsogaming.com](mailto:john2@dsogaming.com)
